Alright, let's try this. Okay, it looks good, but creating a new card isn't great.
There's a simplistic JavaScript pop-up for the name and no way to add a description.
and no way to add a description. This does not look professional.
Not look professional. Can it be improved? All right, we give it its marching orders. We'll see how it does with this, and it's a good example of working iteratively.
It says I've been wrestling with a better UI for card creation."
So obviously it was already thinking about this somewhere in the trace that went by that
I didn't read.
We'll let it do its thing and I'll see you back in a second.
Okay, it claims it has done that.
It says you can now click the dashed ad card button in any column to see the professional
modal.
And you can do npm run dev but it is already running so I don't need to do that
I can I can see here in the terminal that it's that is doing fine
close that terminal
And I'm now going to I'm gonna say accept all and I'm going to bring back up the cambam board here
It is and I'm going to try pressing add card. Oh, oh, oh this is
Better
Okay, I like this
Add card, there it is, it worked.
Very nice.
Okay, I think we'll let Gemini off at this point.
I think this is pretty good.
I sort of prefer to edit it, but still,
I think it's great.
We haven't checked the delete works,
let's try that, yes, delete does work.
All right, I think that is a wrap
for Google anti-gravity for Gemini.
It seems that it's done a fine job.
I like this a lot.
I think it's very nice.
I don't know.
What do you think for me?
I gotta be honest, for today, I'm giving Codex,
the top position, but it is clearly between Codex,
and really, I mean, GPT 5.2 Codex,
the model running in the codecs IDE and that versus Gemini 3 Pro running in
anti-gravity that both did well I give codecs the win but it's really it's your choice.
Maybe you've had completely different answers to me, maybe you've got very different results,
you may have used different models in which case please do share them, share them in Udemy
or email them to me. I'd love to see them. I would love to see what you've got.
Well, we seem to get through a lot today,
but it was just a teaser.
I wanted to give you the flyby of cursor,
copilot, codecs and anti-gravity,
with the overall takeaway being that look
they're all quite similar when the IDE-based agents,
you can see that they often, they have a sidebar
on the left or the right that you can make larger.
They often come with plan mode and an execute mode, although not all of them.
They're mostly agents.md as the way to drive them, but in the case of anti-gravity, it's
the dot agent rules.
And generally you can see a lot of the same stuff in each of them, and you get very familiar
with this.
And really which one you picked depends on which plan you've paid for or which one you
like, or what
the rest of your team are using. Some people are in for GitHub co-pilot, some like cursor,
which was one of the first that I used. And, you know, it's really the one that suits
you and your needs the most. You can do similar things in all of them. And we're going
to pick a couple of them for the next two days for the projects. really for you you can pick whichever one you like.
You can do much the same things and it's more about now the focus turns to
developing the right techniques to use these in the most effective way.
And on that note, tomorrow we'll be doing our first project, the YOLO project.
I hope you feel brave as we go into YOLO mode and at this point you should
congratulate yourself because somehow already you are 20% of
the way through. You're a fifth of the way through the programme but don't worry
that means it's still four-fifths to go and it's going to be so much fun
starting with YOLO tomorrow.